home

As a new global knowledge age dawns, there is need for capacity building within critical target groups especially in the developing countries and elsewhere. In order to harness the potentials for this new age for accelerated socio-economic development  and spur innovation that is a requirement for national survival, Information and Communication Technology provided an environment where FixBiz Solutions operates today in this new age.

Fixbiz Solutions is a start up IT company in Nigeria, offering a full range of services for a wide array of enterprises in both the public and private sectors. Whether you are starting up a new business or already a well-established name, we would be happy to assist you in all your digital needs or projects from conceptualization, business analysis to development and implementation of a such project as well as offering value added services to support an easy and smooth kick off of such platforms. 

You can't afford to miss the opportunity which FixBiz Solutions presents.


about us

Fixbiz Solutions is an information and communication technology firm established in 2015 to address the digital divides which exist presently in the country.

Located in the heart of Nigeria,Fixbiz Solutions is an enterprise which offers technological services such as Web design and application development, ICT consultancy, software development, electronic accounting packages, sales and repairs of personal computers, networking services, online advertising etc.

Our Information Technology professionals are highly qualified and specialized in working on the most up-to-date Information Technology software programs available and also continually stay up-to-date on the newest entries into the industry.

We have left formidable footsteps as a result of our services to our esteemed clients who still enjoy such services till present.  Our mission and Vision has guided our team of trained staff in carrying out their distinguished duties optimally.

Our customers are the reason for our steep growth as their recommendations and word-of-mouth have increased our client base. Our commitment and dedication pays us by prospering relationships with client and make a win-win situation for both sides.

We hope to extend our services all through the country in order to FIX potential challenges and put smiles on our clients face.

Business mgt system

Simplify your employee scheduling with MINDBODY business management software. Cut administrative overhead and improve customer retention with online scheduling and payments, staff and student management, strategic marketing tools and eCommerce solutions. All of your business needs are met online, allowing you to manage and grow your franchise business anywhere, anytime. Schedule a no obligation demo today! 

Web-based accounting, inventory, sales, purchasing and production management software for small and mid-sized businesses. Save your time by having access to your data anywhere at anytime and save your budget by managing all resources of your business with a lower cost. The program is supported in English, Spanish, Korean, Chinese, and Japanese. Free training and support. Start a free 7-day trial today! Makes it easy to track transactions in your store from sales, stock movements, taxes and gross profit, barcodes and label printing.

Billing & Invoicing
eCommerce Management
Employee Management
Financial Management
Inventory Management
Marketing Management
Order Management
Point of Sale (POS)
Purchasing
Time & Expense Tracking
Training Management
Vendor Management

ICT CONSULTANCY
Here at FixBiz Solutions we can add value to your business by providing strategy, architecture, implementation and integration services to help plan, build, improve and innovate your business objectives. We provide these services across a range of technologies and delivery models including mobility, cloud, IT outsourcing, network, communications​, data centre, end-user computing, security, and sustainability.

Our professionals around the world advise you on optimal ways to use technology and services to transform your ICT environment and achieve higher levels of innovation. We help you develop a strategic roadmap that aligns your IT strategy and investments to your business priorities. We also assist in developing specific strategies for mobility, cloud, and IT-as-a-service to help you unlock the potential of these emerging technologies. 

We work with you to architect a holistic solution that integrates new technologies with the legacy environment, in line with your IT strategy.  As par​​​t of any transformation, we identify the required changes to the ICT infrastructure – from network, communications, and security to the data centre, end-user computing, applications, and service management – to ensure the new service delivers the desired return on investment and business outcomes.

As a full life cycle service provider, we will help you implement, integrate, manage and continually improve the solution – across a myriad of operating model options.   We bring a disciplined, systematic approach using time-tested assessments, methodologies, frameworks, and best practices to drive consistency and quality throughout the project engagement.

Our Strategic Consulting Offerings includes:
Information Strategy Planning
IT Cost Analysis and ROI
Internet and Legacy Systems Integration
Capacity Building/Training

repairs
Nothing is more frustrating than something not working when you need it most. Doesn't it seem like your computer always needs repair at the worst times? Perhaps your final paper is due for a class or you simply can't do the work you need to - whatever the case, getting your PC repaired is essential.

Repair services are performed in a timely manner by highly trained, factory technicians using only original parts at FizBiz Solutins. In addition to restoring your device’s functionality, standard repair service includes firmware updates and calibration in adherence to product specifications.

PC Computer Repair & Support Services (partial list)
PC Technical Support
PC Repair / Troubleshooting
PC Setup / Installation
PC Training / Tutoring
System Security Testing
Wired / Wireless Networking
Hardware Upgrades / Installation
Software Upgrades / Installation
Operating System Updates
Anti-Virus Installation / Removal
Motherboard Replacement
Memory Upgrades

Networking service

We offer networking services for home and business. Whether you need a simple network for your home to share printers and Internet access or a robust, fault-tolerant and secure setup for your business, we can help.

Today's small office / home office (SOHO) networking products are made so that anyone can plug one in and get a simple network up and running. Providers such as Megapath offer quality dsl service to support your businesses needs. Along with this ease of use comes a large gap in information security, particularly with wireless networking products, but for the average home user this does not pose a problem.

Making sure no one can access your data or use your shared Internet service without your knowledge or consent is your own responsibility. If someone uses your Internet services to perform illegal activities you may be held accountable.


Networking Setup & Support Services (partial list)
Hubs & Switches
Router Configuration
Network Cabling
Wall Jacks / Paneling
Network Security Testing
Firewalls
Intrusion Detection Systems (IDS)
Virtual Private Networking (VPN)

web design and development

designing attractive, usable web sites that empower your business to succeed is truly an expert skill. In today's crowded web services market many firms can simply create your site, but how many firms can make a web site that succeeds?

In the world of web design, we define success to be targeted visitor traffic coupled with successful delivery of your message or sale of your product/service.

This involves building intelligent, user-centered site features that are both simple and sophisticated. Your web pages also must be highly optimized for fast viewing as well as fully indexable by search engines. The following is a partial listing of our services:

Web Design & Development
Graphic Design
Content Management Systems
Search Engine Optimization
Database Design
Flash Web Design
eCommerce, Shopping Carts

We've developed a six-step lifecycle approach to development projects of any size and type. We begin by learning your goals and identifying which technologies are the most well-suited for you and finish by far exceeding those goals, resulting in the success of your new web project!

Web Site Maintenance
As your business grows and changes, so too will the needs of your web site. Our maintenance services are comprehensive, affordable, and have fast project turnaround times. Why not leave your web site tasks to us so you can better focus on the needs of your business?	Web Site Maintenance

Web Design Portfolio
We've completed web design projects for clients primarily in and around Boston and New England (Massachusetts, Vermont, New Hampshire, Maine, Rhode Island, Connecticut). Unfortunately, at this time, our design portfolio is under construction.

web hosting

Business Web Hosting - In the world of web site hosting, where there exist tens of thousands of companies across the globe that provide all sorts of features over a wide range of prices, how does one choose the right web hosting company for their business?

eCommerce Web Hosting - Whether your solution involves an extensive online catalogue of products having search capabilities or just the ability to process credit card transactions in realtime, we can help you.

Email Hosting - Worry free and very easy-to-use. The best choice for hosting your company's email accounts. Includes complex spam filtering free of charge.


Customer Service & Support - 

At BCN, customer service and technical support are our highest priorities! Whether you are a local Masschusetts, New Hampshire, Vermont, Maine, Connecticut, or Rhode Island customer that has shaken hands with us, or you are elsewhere, you will receive the best quality support for your needs.

digital  marketing

Digital marketing in Nigeria has become more competitive than ever and merely posting good content is never adequate to prosper. Kordahi marketing team have experienced professionals for monitoring social consoles, running contest, sweepstakes and bringing more engagement on-board. Being one of the most creative SEO companies in Nigeria, Kordahi Technologies is good at targeting key areas and audience that actually cares about your business. Increasing clicks, configuring Google ads and page-views per day is our prime focus for your website.

Search Engine Optimization
SEM/SMO
Pay Per Click
Content Creation and Marketing
Online Reputation Management

software development

We understand that every business has special software requirements that off-the-shelf software solutions cannot solve. Our customer-centred approach enables our developers to capture your business requirements and develop a fully customised software solution that solves your unique business needs.
If you are looking for a reliable software development company to enhance your business performance, that differentiates you from your competitors and helps you become more cost efficient, you have come to the right place. Our software services has helped our clients achieve the following :-
High quality solutions that tailor fit the business requirements
Scalable solution that grows with client requirement
Streamlining customer business work-flow
Productivity Improvement
Reduction in overheads and increase in ROI

E-LEARNING

At Lynx Training and Development,we in collaboration with our partners have managed to assemble a community of professionals from government institutions, non-governmental organizations, private corporations and educational institutions working in the eLearning industry in the developing world. It was founded to address the need for a hub for sharing information and resources in e-Learning and for collaboration in the development and implementation of e-Learning courses and projects through new and advanced technology.

t Lynx Training, we provide value to our stakeholders and corporate partners by innovation, accomplishment, trust and long-term relationships through our unique service network portfolio of e-Learning expertise. We are a group of highly resilient people committed to e-Learning implementation and embrace all challenges to convert them into meaningful solutions.